Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963 - 1994 UA.03.61.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
H. Keith H. Brodie, President, records
1963 - 1994
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Brodie, H. Keith H. (Harlow Keith Hammond), 1939-
UA.03.61.0001
178.5 Linear Feet
H. Keith H. Brodie came to Duke in 1974 as professor and chairman of the Department of Psychiatry and director of Psychiatric Services at Duke University Medical Center. Dr. Brodie served as Duke's Chancellor from 1982 to 1985 and as Duke's President from 1985 to 1993. Collection includes university administrative records, personal papers, manuscripts, photographs, printed matter, memorabilia, and other material created or received by Dr. Brodie during his tenure as President, 1985-1993. Included are materials generated by the inauguration of Dr. Brodie as president of Duke University, Dr. Leslie Banner's working files for speeches and other presentations given by President Brodie, and subject files containing correspondence, memoranda, speeches, reports, and other materials. Subjects include admissions, the Academic Council, alumni, committees and campaigns, athletics, The Duke Endowment, various university departments, the Medical Center, and Student Affairs. English.
120,000 Items
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Unprocessed materials are closed pending processing.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records was received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1985-2004.
Biographical Note
H. Keith H. Brodie received his M.D. in 1965 from Columbia University. He served at hospitals in New Orleans and New York City before becoming a clinical associate with the National Institute of Mental Health in 1968. In 1970, he joined the medical faculty of Stanford University. He came to Duke in 1974 as professor and chairman of the Department of Psychiatry and director of Psychiatric Services at Duke University Medical Center. Dr. Brodie served as Duke's Chancellor from 1982 to 1985 and as Duke's President from 1985 to 1993. His memoir of his presidency, Keeping An Open Door, coauthored with Leslie Banner, was published by Duke Press in 1996.
During his tenure, applications to Duke's graduate and undergraduate programs increased greatly as the school became a nationally known research university. Academic initiatives included the establishment of an Institute of Statistics and Decision Sciences and a new School of the Environment. Interdisciplinary planning was reflected in a new science building, the Levine Science Research Center, which brought together faculty from varied disciplines. Other capital projects added a dormitory, a building for policy sciences and public affairs, medical research buildings, and the campus wide network, DukeNet. Duke made efforts to increase the number of African-Americans in academia with a Black Faculty Initiative and a Program for Preparing Minorities for Academic Careers. Increased faculty participation in the governance of the University was made possible by the establishment of the President's Advisory Council on Resources.
Collection Overview
Collection includes university administrative records, personal papers, manuscripts, photographs, printed matter, memorabilia, and other material created or received by Dr. Brodie during his tenure as President, 1985-1993. Included are materials generated by the inauguration of Dr. Brodie as president of Duke University, Dr. Leslie Banner's working files for speeches and other presentations given by President Brodie, and subject files containing correspondence, memoranda, speeches, reports, and other materials. Subjects include admissions, the Academic Council, alumni, committees and campaigns, athletics, The Duke Endowment, various university departments, the Medical Center, and Student Affairs.
Related Material
H. Keith H. Brodie, Chancellor, Records, 1970-1985
Duke University Archives
Oral history interview with H. Keith H. Brodie, 2004
Duke University Medical Center Library
H. Keith H. Brodie and Leslie Banner
The Research University Presidency in the Late Twentieth Century: A Life Cycle/Case History Approach. Westport, Conn.: Praeger Publishers, 12005
H. Keith H. Brodie and Leslie Banner
Keeping an Open Door: Passages in a University Presidency. Durham, NC: Duke University Press, 1996
Universities and colleges -- North Carolina -- History -- 20th century; Education, Higher -- North Carolina -- History; Duke University. Presidents; Duke University -- Presidents; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University. Medical Center; Duke University. Board of Trustees; Duke Endowment; Duke University -- Administration; Brodie, H. Keith H. (Harlow Keith Hammond), 1939-; Brodie, H. Keith H. (Harlow Keith Hammond), 1939-; Banner, Leslie
- Inauguration of H. Keith H. Brodie, 1985 Accession UA85-134.
  Scope and Contents note
  Materials generated by the inauguration of Dr. Brodie as president of Duke University. Included are invitations, programs, announcements, a press packet, press clippings, and greetings from other institutions.
  - Programs (Box 1)
    Invitations, Programs, Announcements, a press packet, press clippings, and other materials regarding the inauguration.
  - Greetings (Box 2)
    Greetings from colleges and universities and other institutions in celebration of the inauguration.
- Working Files for Speeches and Presentations, 1985-1994 and undated
  This series contains source and background material, drafts, and other working files for speeches and presentations given by Dr. Brodie. They are arranged in two sub-series. The first subseries is the working files of Dr. Leslie Banner, coauthor of Dr. Brodie's speeches. The second subseries is the working files of Dr. Brodie.
  Drafts and final versions of many of these same speeches are in boxes 76-78.
  Arrangement note
  Files are arranged in roughly chronological order with some deviations.
  - Working Files for Speeches and Presentations, 1985-1993 and undated. Accession UA94-8. (Box 3)
    Dr. Leslie Banner's working files for speeches and other presentations given by President Brodie. The files include source materials, correspondence, clippings, schedules, interview notes, and other related materials as well as drafts and final versions of speeches.
    - Convocation, 1985 Aug. 21 (Box 3)
    - Quarter Century Club, 1985 Sept. 13 (Box 3)
    - Inaugural Dinner: Rosovksy Introduction, 1985 Sept. 27 (Box 3)
    - Alumni Reception Remarks, Charlotte, NC, 1985 Oct. 11 (Box 3)
    - Remarks: Gerontology Building Dedication, 1985 Oct. 12 (Box 3)
    - Alumni Reception Remarks, Chicago, 1985 Oct. 9 (Box 3)
    - Chicago Address, 1985 Oct. 9 (Box 3)
    - Speech: Benjamin N. Duke Leadership Fund, 1985 Oct. 15 (Box 3)
    - NC Egg Marketing Assoc. Recipe, 1985 Oct. 17 (Box 3)
    - Engineering: Dean's Council Speech, 1985 Nov. 15 (Box 3)
    - Luncheon Remarks: Institute of Policy Sciences, 1985 Nov. 8 (Box 3)
    - Speech: Watauga Club, 1985 Nov. 5 (Box 3)
    - Duke Seminar Speech, 1985 Nov. 2 (Box 3)
    - Tree Lighting Speech, 1985 Dec. 2 (Box 3)
    - Duke Endowment Dinner Speech, 1985 Dec. 2 (Box 3)
    - Dedication of the Gallery of Presidents, 1985 Dec. 7 (Box 3)
    - Duke/Durham Luncheon Address, 1985 Dec. 8 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Society Dinner: Speech by Mary Semans, 1985 Dec. 7 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Weekend Research and Notes, 1985 Dec. 6-1985 Dec. 8 (Box 3)
    - January Freshman Speech, 1986 Jan. 3 (Box 3)
    - Luncheon Remarks for College of Bishops, 1986 Jan. 9 (Box 3)
    - Speech: Faculty and Staff Solicitation, 1986 Jan. 30 (Box 3)
    - NC Press Awards Presentation, 1986 Jan. 31 (Box 3)
    - Job Enhancement Speech, 1986 Feb. 3 (Box 3)
    - Bryan Research Center Dedication, 1986 Feb. 12 (Box 3)
    - Cities Chairmen Speech, 1986 Feb. 21 (Box 3)
    - Panhellenic and Inter-Fraternity Council Speech, 1986 Mar. 11 (Box 3)
    - Address to Black Applicants, 1986 Mar. 13 (Box 3)
    - Centurion Dinner, 1986 Sept. 26 (Box 3)
    - Luncheon Hudson Family, 1986 Sept. 27 (Box 3)
    - Reunion Gift Presentation, 1986 Sept. 27 (Box 3)
    - Quarter Century Banquet, 1986 Sept. 30 (Box 3)
    - Fuqua Symposium on US & South Africa, 1986 Oct. 2 (Box 3)
    - Secondary School Counselor Conference, 1986 Oct. 9 (Box 3)
    - Introduction of Robert S. McNamara, 1986 Oct. 15 (Box 3)
    - Inauguration of Spangler, 1986 Oct. 17 (Box 3)
    - Neil Williams Speech for Homecoming Weekend, 1986 Oct. 24-1986 Oct. 25 (Box 3)
    - Remarks to Class of 1946, 1986 Nov. 7 (Box 3)
    - Introduction of Peter Williams, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 3)
    - Tree Lighting, 1986 Dec. 2 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Day Convocation. Medals: Mary Semans, Taylor Cole, 1986 Dec. 11 (Box 3)
    - FDR'S SOC Dinner, 1986 Dec. 13 (Box 3)
    - Soccer Team Welcome, 1986 Dec. 15 (Box 3)
    - Hough Introduction, 1987 Jan. 21 (Box 3)
    - NC Press Association Dinner, 1987 Jan. 30 (Box 3)
    - BOT Weekend, 1987 Feb. 27 (Box 3)
    - Raleigh Alumni Meeting (Blue Devil Presentation), 1987 Mar. 17 (Box 3)
    - Brenda Brodie Speech, 1987 Apr. 3 (Box 3)
    - Cancer Center Welcome, 1987 Apr. 15 (Box 3)
    - Trustee Dinner, 1987 May 8 (Box 3)
    - Acceptance of Gift from Class of 1937, 1987 May 9 (Box 3)
    - David Thomas Luncheon and Fuqua Groundbreaking, 1987 May 9 (Box 3)
    - Honorary Degree Dinner, 1987 May 9 (Box 3)
    - TIP Welcome: Gov. Introduced, 1987 May 15 (Box 3)
    - Commencement. Honorary Degrees: Edward Koppel, Eppie Lederer, R. David Thomas, Mary Good, Thomas Powell. Distinguished Alumni: Reynolds Price, 1987 May 10 (Box 3)
    - Management Day, 1987 June 1 (Box 3)
    - American Dance Festival Opening Remarks, 1987 June 7 (Box 3)
    - Baccalaureate Service, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Grad Student's Convocation, 1987 Aug. 28 (Box 3)
    - Trustee Dinner: Barringer Gift and Pye Tribute, 1987 Sept. 25 (Box 3)
    - Smullin Dedication, 1987 Oct. 8 (Box 3)
    - Steve Spurrier Introduction, undated (Box 3)
    - Quarter Century Banquet, 1987 Oct. 12 (Box 3)
    - Trent Dinner, 1987 Nov. 12 (Box 3)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1987 Dec. 1 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Day Convocation. Medals: Juanita Kreps, Reynolds Price, 1987 Dec. 10 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Day, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Centurion Dinner, 1987 Dec. 11 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Day Convocation, 1987 Dec. 10 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Day, 1984 Nov.-1989 June 30 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Society Dinner, 1987 Dec. 12 (Box 3)
    - Founders' Breakfast and Lector Notes, 1987 Dec. 13 (Box 3)
    - NC Press Association Awards, 1988 Jan. 22 (Box 4)
    - Reagan Visit: Substance Abuse, 1988 Feb. 8 (Box 4)
    - Trustee Dinner, 1988 Feb. 26 (Box 4)
    - Groundbreaking for New Dormitory, 1988 Mar. 2 (Box 4)
    - Address to Black Applicants, 1988 Mar. 17 (Box 4)
    - Academic Council Statement Re: Reagan Visit, 1988 Mar. 17 (Box 4)
    - Baccalaureate Services, 1988 May 6-1988 May 7 (Box 4)
    - Trustee Dinner: Ascher, Phil Stewart, Charlie Clotfelter, John Forlines, Neil Williams, 1988 May 6 (Box 4)
    - Dinner Honorary Degrees and Alumni Award, 1988 May 7 (Box 4)
    - Commencement. Honorary Degrees: John Cocke, Cathleen Morawetz, Garry Trudeau, Kenneth Clark, Robert Shaw. Distinguished Alumni: Edwin Jones, 1988 May 8 (Box 4)
    - Garry B. Trudeau, undated (Box 4)
    - Acceptance of Gift from Class of 1938, 1988 May 7 (Box 4)
    - Boston Alumni Dinner, 1988 May 18 (Box 4)
    - AMA Conference on Adolescent Health, 1988 June 9 (Box 4)
    - Marine Lab 50th, 1988 June 11 (Box 4)
    - Tribute to Neil Williams, 1988 June 14 (Box 4)
    - Opening Convocation, 1988 Aug. 24 (Box 4)
    - Eye Center Groundbreaking, 1988 Aug. 22 (Box 4)
    - Presentation to Jesse Jackson, 1988 Aug. 28 (Box 4)
    - Lector: Opening of School Year 1988, 1988 Sept. 4 (Box 4)
    - AT&T Gift Announcement, 1988 Sept. 13 (Box 4)
    - Parent's Committee Dinner Meeting, 1987 Sept. 18 (Box 4)
    - Centurion Dinner, 1988 Sept. 24 (Box 4)
    - Tribute to Dr. Anlyan, 1988 Sept. 23 (Box 4)
    - Tribute to Sam Katz, 1988 Sept. 30 (Box 4)
    - J. Walter Thompson Archives Reception, 1988 Sept. 26 (Box 4)
    - Quarter Century Banquet, 1988 Oct. 13 (Box 4)
    - Dupont Plaque, 1988 Oct. 31 (Box 4)
    - United Negro College Fund Breakfast, 1988 Nov. 9 (Box 4)
    - Goldwater Honor, 1988 Nov. 10 (Box 4)
    - American Tobacco Press Conference, 1988 Nov. 11 (Box 4)
    - Tree Lighting Ceremony, 1988 Nov. 29 (Box 4)
    - Founders' Day Lector Notes, 1988 Dec. 11 (Box 4)
    - Founders' Breakfast, 1988 Dec. 11 (Box 4)
    - Founders' Dinner, 1988 Dec. 10 (Box 4)
    - Trustees' Dinner, 1988 Dec. 9 (Box 4)
    - Founders' Convocation. Medals: Walter McGowan Upchurch, Jr., Richard Watson, 1988 Dec. 8 (Box 4)
    - Speech: Duke Seminar, 1986 Jan. 24 (Box 4)
    - Address to the Council on Women's Studies, 1986 Feb. 27 (Box 4)
    - Trustees' Dinner, 1986 Feb. 28 (Box 4)
    - Speech: Address to Black Applicants, 1986 Mar. 13 (Box 4)
    - Speech: Divinity Board of Visitors, 1986 Mar. 14 (Box 4)
    - Speech: ASDU Legislature, 1986 Mar. 24 (Box 4)
    - A. B. Duke Scholarship Finalists, 1986 Apr. 4 (Box 4)
    - Speech: Atlanta, 1986 May 31 (Box 4)
    - Commencement. Honorary Degrees: Robert Mayer Lumiansky, Kenneth Royall, Terry Sanford, Ralph O. Slatyer, Lee A. lacocca. Distinguished Alumni Award: Mary Semans, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Speech: Public Safety Dinner, 1986 June 11 (Box 4)
    - Opening Convocation: Welcome to the Chapel, 1986 Aug. 27 (Box 4)
    - Third World Conference, 1986 Sept. 25 (Box 4)
    - Address to the N.C. Conference of the United Methodist Church, 1986 June 2 (Box 4)
    - Speech: Lake Junaluska Methodists, 1986 June 6 (Box 4)
    - R. David Thomas Speech, 1986 June 13 (Box 4)
    - Lector Notes: Chapel Service for Legislat, 1989 Jan. 22 (Box 5)
    - Campaign for Duke, 1989 Feb. 16 (Box 5)
    - Women's Studies 150th Symposium, 1989 Mar. 3 (Box 5)
    - CIDR Dinner and Sanford Intro, 1989 Apr. 7 (Box 5)
    - Confronting Rape Culture Colloquium, 1989 Apr. 8 (Box 5)
    - KROC Award, 1989 Apr. 10 (Box 5)
    - J. B. Fuqua Bust Unveiling, 1989 Apr. 14 (Box 5)
    - Black Academic Surgeons and Sullivan. Tribute to Charles Watts, 1989 Apr. 13 (Box 5)
    - Bishops of United Methodist Church, 1989 May 1 (Box 5)
    - Baccalaureate Lector Notes, 1989 May 13 (Box 5)
    - Trustee Dinner, 1989 May 12 (Box 5)
    - Commencement Honorees Dinner, 1989 May 13 (Box 5)
    - Commencement, 1989 May 14 (Box 5)
    - David Cogan, undated (Box 5)
    - Patricia M. Derian, undated (Box 5)
    - F. Sherwood Rowland, undated (Box 5)
    - Stephen J. Gould, undated (Box 5)
    - Academic Council: Report on Women and African-American Faculty, 1989 Sept. 21 (Box 5)
    - Duke Family Reunion Tea, 1989 Sept. 30 (Box 5)
    - Duke Endowment Dinner, 1989 Oct. 2 (Box 5)
    - Quarter Century Banquet, 1989 Oct. 5 (Box 5)
    - National Humanities Center: Installation of Robert Connor, 1989 Oct. 20 (Box 5)
    - International Studies, 1989 Oct. 20 (Box 5)
    - R. David Thomas Center Dedication, 1989 Oct. 27 (Box 5)
    - Trinity Board of Visitors, 1989 Nov. 17 (Box 5)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1989 Dec. 4 (Box 5)
    - Convocation, 1989 Dec. 7 (Box 5)
    - Convocation: Kenneth Goodson, Marcus Hobbes, 1989 Dec. (Box 5)
    - Centurion Dinner, 1989 Dec. 9 (Box 5)
    - Sower Presentations, 1989 Dec. 9 (Box 5)
    - Schaefer House Luncheon and Dedication, 1989 Dec. 9 (Box 5)
    - Founders Breakfast, 1989 Dec. 10 (Box 5)
    - Founders Lector Notes, 1989 Dec. 10 (Box 5)
    - All American Bowl, 1989 Dec. 12 (Box 5)
    - D. Allan Bromley, 1990 Jan. 25 (Box 5)
    - Paul B. Williams Media Center, 1990 Feb. 21 (Box 5)
    - Bryan Neurobiology Center Dedication, 1990 Feb. 22 (Box 5)
    - C. Eric Lincoln: Howard Johnson Award, 1990 Feb. 23 (Box 5)
    - Campaign for Duke, 1990 Feb. 24 (Box 5)
    - Dave Stedman Citation (NCCBI), 1990 Mar. 21 (Box 5)
    - Stedman folder, undated (Box 5)
    - Youth Education Day, 1990 Apr. 14 (Box 5)
    - Humanitarian Service Award: Neil Boothby, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Julian Abele Banquet, 1990 Apr. 20 (Box 6)
    - Earth Day, 1990 Apr. 22 (Box 6)
    - Trent Society, Lawrence J. Friedman, 1990 Apr. 26 (Box 6)
    - Washington Alumni Speech, 1990 May 1 (Box 6)
    - Washington Alumni Speech, 1990 May 1 (Box 6)
    - Baccalaureate Service, 1990 May 11 (Box 6)
    - Trustee Dinner. Tribute to John Day, Award for Merit to Allan Kornberg, Andy Wallace, 1990 May 11 (Box 6)
    - Commencement Honorees Dinner. Honorary Degrees: Dave Palmer, Tom Brokaw, Professor Georges Balandier (not able to attend), 1990 May 12 (Box 6)
    - Palmer, Dave R., undated (Box 6)
    - Brokaw, undated (Box 6)
    - Commencement Senior Letter, 1990 May 13 (Box 6)
    - Commencement, 1990 May 13 (Box 6)
    - Herbert Pardes, 1990 May 13 (Box 6)
    - Employee Recognition Week, 1990 June 4-1990 June 9 (Box 6)
    - Charles Johnson Dinner, 1990 Sept. 14 (Box 6)
    - Lord Symposium, 1990 Sept. 25 (Box 6)
    - Semans Dinner, 1990 Sept. 27 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report, 1990 Sept. 28 (Box 6)
    - J. Walter Thompson Reception, 1990 Oct. 3 (Box 6)
    - Centurions Dinner, 1990 Oct. 5 (Box 6)
    - Quarter Century Banquet, 1990 Oct. 11 (Box 6)
    - Eye Center Dedication, 1990 Oct. 12 (Box 6)
    - Duke Endowment Dinner, 1990 Oct. 1 (Box 6)
    - Lilly Gift Reception, 1990 Nov. 17 (Box 6)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1990 Dec. 4 (Box 6)
    - Founders Convocation. Distinguished Alumni Award: L. Neil Williams, Jr. University Medal: Mary Grace Wilson, Charles Wade, 1990 Dec. 6 (Box 6)
    - Mary Grace Wilson, undated (Box 6)
    - Charles B. Wade, Jr., undated (Box 6)
    - Founders Dinner, Reception, Breakfast, 1990 Dec. 8-1990 Dec. 9 (Box 6)
    - Founders Lector Notes, 1990 Dec. 9 (Box 6)
    - Founders Awards and Recognitions, undated (Box 6)
    - Convocation: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 6)
    - Martin Luther King Celebration, 1991 Jan. 21 (Box 7)
    - NAS/IOM Regional Roundtable, 1991 Jan. 28 (Box 7)
    - Elected Officials Sunday Lector Notes, 1991 Feb. 3 (Box 7)
    - J. Peter Grace Introduction, 1991 Feb. 25 (Box 7)
    - Betsy Locke Interview, 1991 Feb. 26 (Box 7)
    - Introduction of Dan Blue, 1991 Mar. 7 (Box 7)
    - Ozal Luncheon, 1991 Mar. 26 (Box 7)
    - Educating for Science Forum: Introduction of Philip Griffiths, 1991 Mar. 26 (Box 7)
    - Women's Studies Symposium, 1991 Apr. 5 (Box 7)
    - C. Eric Lincoln Tribute, 1991 Apr. 5 (Box 7)
    - Sanford Distinguished Lecture Welcome, 1991 Apr. 11 (Box 7)
    - Bill Griffith Dinner, 1991 Apr. 12 (Box 7)
    - Basketball Awards Banquet, 1991 Apr. 15 (Box 7)
    - Trinity Board of Visitors, 1991 Apr. 19 (Box 7)
    - Julian Abele Banquet, 1991 Apr. 20 (Box 7)
    - Board of Trustees, 1991 May 10 (Box 7)
    - Baccalaureate Lector Notes, 1991 May 10 (Box 7)
    - Trustees Dinner: Tribute to Jerry Hudson, 1991 May 10 (Box 7)
    - Honorary Degree Dinner, 1991 May 11 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1991 May 12 (Box 7)
    - Commencement Script, 1991 May 12 (Box 7)
    - Letter to Seniors Re Commencement, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Georges Balandier, undated (Box 7)
    - Gertrude B. Elion, undated (Box 7)
    - Eleanor Cutri Smeal, undated (Box 7)
    - Charles D. Watts, undated (Box 7)
    - George F. Will, undated (Box 7)
    - Commencement Luncheon, 1991 May 12 (Box 7)
    - Employee Appreciation Week, 1991 May 15 (Box 7)
    - Scholarship Brochure, 1991 Sept. (Box 7)
    - United Way Kickoff, 1991 Sept. 5 (Box 7)
    - Trustees Dinner: Tribute to Philip Griffiths, 1991 Sept. 27 (Box 7)
    - Goodson Memorial Service, 1991 Sept. 30 (Box 7)
    - Duke Endowment Dinner, 1991 Sept. 30 (Box 7)
    - Duke Endowment Dinner, 1991 Sept. 30 (Box 7)
    - President's Council Seminar, 1991 Oct. 31 (Box 7)
    - Leon Levine Letter, 1991 Nov. 6 (Box 7)
    - President's Letter to the Senior Class, 1991 Nov. 7 (Box 7)
    - Trinity College Board of Visitors, 1991 Nov. 8 (Box 7)
    - Arts and Sciences Brochure, 1991 Nov. 11 (Box 7)
    - Asian/Pacific Studies Institute, 1991 Nov. 19 (Box 7)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1991 Dec. 4 (Box 7)
    - Founders' Day Convocation, 1991 Dec. 5 (Box 7)
    - University Medals, undated (Box 7)
    - Marshall Pickens, undated (Box 7)
    - William Styron, undated (Box 7)
    - Teaching Awards, undated (Box 7)
    - Humanitarian Service Award, undated (Box 7)
    - University/Scholar Teacher, undated (Box 7)
    - Alumni Undergraduate Teaching Award, undated (Box 7)
    - Convocation Continued, undated (Box 7)
    - Trustee Dinner, 1991 Dec. 6 (Box 7)
    - Susan King, undated (Box 7)
    - Founders' Reception, Dinner, Breakfast, 1991 Dec. 7-1991 Dec. 8 (Box 7)
    - Founders' Lector Notes, 1991 Dec. 8 (Box 7)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1991 Jan. 20 (Box 7)
    - Oldham CV, undated (Box 7)
    - Duke Seminar, 1992 Jan. 31 (Box 7)
    - Presidential Awards Luncheon, 1992 Feb. 11 (Box 8)
    - Matt Sclafani Memorial Service, 1992 Feb. 13 (Box 8)
    - A. B. Duke Scholarship Letter, 1992 Feb. 14 (Box 8)
    - Laettner Jersey Retirement, 1992 Feb. 26 (Box 8)
    - Centurion Dinner, 1992 Feb. 28 (Box 8)
    - 1492: Introduction of Frank Donatelli, 1992 Feb. 29 (Box 8)
    - McFarlane Letter, 1992 Mar. 12 (Box 8)
    - Letter to Seniors, 1992 Mar. 20 (Box 8)
    - Philip Morris Proposal, 1992 Mar. 31 (Box 8)
    - NCAA Basketball Champions Homecoming, 1992 Apr. 7 (Box 8)
    - Memorial Service for William Zung, 1992 Apr. 8 (Box 8)
    - American Dance Festival Statement, 1992 Apr. 10 (Box 8)
    - Duke/Durham Campaign, 1992 Apr. 22 (Box 8)
    - Academic Council, 1992 Apr. 23 (Box 8)
    - Rodney King Rally, 1992 May 1 (Box 8)
    - SRC files, undated (6 folders) (Box 8)
    - SRI Brochure, undated (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - APA Badge Presentation, 1992 May 3 (Box 8)
    - Employee Appreciation Week Letter, 1992 May 6 (Box 8)
    - Dinner for Ed Pratt, 1992 Feb. 25 (Box 8)
    - Ed Pratt, undated (Box 8)
    - Dinner Honoring Ed Pratt/Pfizer, 1992 May 14 (Box 8)
    - George Herbert, undated (Box 8)
    - Trustee Dinner to honor Ken Royall, 1992 May 15 (Box 8)
    - Commencement Luncheon, 1992 May 17 (Box 8)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients Dinner, 1992 May 16 (Box 8)
    - Commencement, 1992 May 17 (Box 8)
    - Graduation Reception, undated (Box 8)
    - Elna Spaulding, undated (Box 8)
    - Marian Wright Edelman, undated (Box 8)
    - A. Kenneth Pye, undated (Box 8)
    - Robert R. Everett, undated (Box 8)
    - James D. Ebert, undated (Box 8)
    - Lector Notes, undated (Box 8)
    - Employee Appreciation Week, 1992 May 28 (Box 8)
    - Law School Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1992 Sept. 19 (Box 9)
    - Ken Royall Letter, 1992 Sept. 24 (Box 9)